Guide to the Poly Archives Historic Photograph Collection RG.026
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
- Series VI: Alumni
  - Subseries D: Alumni Leadership Seminar
    - Alumni Leadership Seminar, 1995 October 2; cuid618 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Alumni Leadership Seminar, John Sie, 1995 October 23; cuid619 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Alumni Leadership Seminar, Rachel Freidman, 1996 October 10; cuid620 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Alumni Leadership Seminar, William Mow, 1996- November 4; cuid621 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Alumni Leadership Seminar, John Giba, 1996 November 11; cuid622 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Alumni Leadership Seminar, Leon Levy, 1998 May 1; cuid623 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Alumni Leadership Seminar, Gerald Ross, 1998 September 25; cuid624 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Alumni Leadership Seminar,Nicholas Reitenbach, 1998 October 26; cuid625 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Alumni Leadership Seminar, Charles Souter, 1998 November 18; cuid626 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - Alumni Leadership Seminar, Daniel Greenberg, 1999; cuid627 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - Alumni Leadership Lunch, 1999 March; cuid628 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - Alumni Leadership Seminar, Robert Prieto, 1999 March 11; cuid629 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - Alumni Leadership Seminar, Stanley Beige, 1999 April 4; cuid630 (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - Alumni Leadership Seminar, Joseph Owades, 1999 April 21; cuid631 (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - Alumni Leadership Seminar, David Sobin, 1999 September 29; cuid632 (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - Alumni Leadership Seminar, Donald Weisstuch, 1999 September 29; cuid633 (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - Alumni Leadership Seminar, Tsuneo Nakahara, 1999 October 4; cuid634 (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - Alumni Leadership Seminar, John Wallace, 1999 October 27; cuid635 (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - Alumni Leadership Seminar, Dr. Peter Bingham, 2000 March 8; cuid636 (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - Alumni Leadership Seminar, Hazel O'Leary, 2000 October 18; cuid637 (Box 15A, Folder 1)
    - Alumni Leadership Seminar, Hazel O'Leary, 2000 October 18; cuid3581 (Box 15A, Folder 2)
    - Alumni Leadership Seminar, Barry Singer, 2001 February 28; cuid638 (Box 15A, Folder 3)
    - Alumni Leadership Seminar, Daniel Robinson, 2001 April 4; cuid639 (Box 15A, Folder 5)
    - Alumni Leadership Seminar, Daniel Robinson, 2001 April 4; cuid3583 (Box 15A, Folder 6)
    - Alumni Leadership Seminar, Michael Kappaz, 2001 April 16; cuid640 (Box 15A, Folder 7)
    - Alumni Leadership Seminar, Michael Kappaz, 2001 April 16; cuid3584 (Box 15A, Folder 8)
  - Subseries E: Alumni Reunion
    - Annual Reunions, undated; cuid641 (Box 15A, Folder 9)
    - Alumni Reunion 1986, cuid642 (Box 15A, Folder 10)
    - Alumni Reunion 1993, cuid643 (Box 15A, Folder 11)
    - Alumni Reunion 1996, 1996 June 8; cuid644 (Box 15A, Folder 12)
    - Alumni Reunion 2002, 2002 June; cuid645 (Box 15A, Folder 13)
    - Alumni Reunion of New York Society for Coatings Technology 1995, 1995 September 12; cuid646 (Box 15A, Folder 14)
    - E.E. Reunion, 2000; cuid647 (Box 15A, Folder 15)
    - Golden Jubilee 1966, 1966 June; cuid648 (Box 15A, Folder 17)
    - Golden Jubilee 1967, 1967 June 15; cuid649 (Box 15A, Folder 18)
    - Golden Jubilee 1984, 1984 July 26; cuid650 (Box 15A, Folder 19)
    - Golden Jubilee 1993, 1993 June; cuid651 (Box 15A, Folder 20)
    - Golden Jubilee 1998, 1998 June 7; cuid652 (Box 15A, Folder 21)
    - Golden Jubilee 1999, 1999 June 5; cuid653 (Box 15A, Folder 23)
    - Golden Jubilee 1999, 1999 June 5; cuid654 (Box 15A, Folder 24)
    - Golden Jubilee 1999, 1999 June 5; cuid3587 (Box 15A, Folder 25)
    - Golden Jubilee 1999, 1999 June 5; cuid3588 (Box 15A, Folder 26)
    - Golden Jubilee 1999 Negatives, 1999 June 5; cuid3589 (Box 15A, Folder 27)
    - Golden Jubilee 2000, 2000 June 5; cuid655 (Box 15A, Folder 28)
    - Golden Jubilee 2000 Negatives, 2000 June 5; cuid3590 (Box 15A, Folder 29)
    - Golden Jubilee 2001, 2001 June 2; cuid656 (Box 15B, Folder 1)
    - Golden Jubilee 2001 Negatives, 2001 June 2; cuid3591 (Box 15B, Folder 2)
    - Silver Jubilee 1999, 1999 June 8; cuid657 (Box 15B, Folder 3)
    - Silver Jubilee 1999, 1999 June 8; cuid3592 (Box 15B, Folder 4)
    - Silver Jubilee 1999, 1999 June 8; cuid3593 (Box 15B, Folder 5)
    - Silver Jubilee 2001, 2001 June 11; cuid658 (Box 15B, Folder 6)
    - Silver Jubilee 2001, 2001 June; cuid3594 (Box 15B, Folder 7)
    - Silver Jubilee 2001, 2001 June 5; cuid659 (Box 15B, Folder 8)
- Series VII: Events
  - Subseries A: Freshman Week (Orientation)
    - Freshman Week 1957, cuid660 (Box 15B, Folder 9)
    - Freshman Week 1997, 1997 August 25; cuid661 (Box 15B, Folder 10)
    - Freshman Week 1997, 1997 August 25; cuid662 (Box 15B, Folder 11)
    - Freshman Week 1998, cuid663 (Box 15C, Folder 4)
    - Freshman Week 1999, 1999 September 1; cuid664 (Box 15C, Folder 5)
    - Freshman Week 2000, 2000 August; cuid665 (Box 15C, Folder 8)
    - Freshman Week 2001, 2001 August 28; cuid666 (Box 15C, Folder 9)
    - Freshman Week 2002, 2002 August 28; cuid667 (Box 15C, Folder 12)
  - Subseries B: Commencement and Convocation
    - Commencement 1946, cuid668 (Box 16A, Folder 1)
    - Commencement 1952, cuid669 (Box 16A, Folder 2)
    - Commencement 1956, cuid670 (Box 16A, Folder 3)
    - Commencement 1958, cuid671 (Box 16A, Folder 4)
    - Commencement 1959, cuid672 (Box 16A, Folder 5)
    - Commencement 1960, cuid673 (Box 16A, Folder 6)
    - Commencement 1961, cuid674 (Box 16A, Folder 7)
    - Commencement 1962, cuid675 (Box 16A, Folder 8)
    - Commencement 1963, cuid676 (Box 16A, Folder 9)
    - Commencement 1964, cuid677 (Box 16A, Folder 10)
    - Commencement 1965, cuid678 (Box 16A, Folder 11)
    - Commencement 1966, cuid679 (Box 16A, Folder 12)
    - Commencement 1967, cuid680 (Box 16A, Folder 13)
    - Commencement 1967, cuid681 (Box 16A, Folder 14)
    - Commencement 1968, cuid682 (Box 16A, Folder 15)
    - Commencement 1969, cuid683 (Box 16A, Folder 16)
    - Commencement 1971, cuid684 (Box 16A, Folder 17)
    - Commencement 1972, cuid685 (Box 16A, Folder 18)
    - Commencement 1973, cuid686 (Box 16A, Folder 19)
    - Commencement 1974, cuid687 (Box 16B, Folder 1)
    - Commencement 1975, 1975 May 30; cuid688 (Box 16B, Folder 2)
    - Commencement 1976, cuid689 (Box 16B, Folder 3)
    - Commencement 1980, cuid690 (Box 16B, Folder 4)
    - Commencement 1981, cuid691 (Box 16B, Folder 5)
    - Commencement 1982, cuid692 (Box 16B, Folder 6)
    - Commencement 1983, cuid693 (Box 16B, Folder 7)
    - Commencement 1985, cuid694 (Box 16B, Folder 8)
    - Commencement 1986, cuid695 (Box 16B, Folder 9)
    - Commencement 1987, 1987 June; cuid696 (Box 16B, Folder 10)
    - Commencement 1988, cuid697 (Box 16B, Folder 11)
    - Commencement 1989, cuid698 (Box 16B, Folder 12)
    - Commencement 1993, cuid699 (Box 16B, Folder 13)
    - Commencement 1994, cuid700 (Box 16C, Folder 1)
    - Commencement 2010, cuid701 (Box 16C, Folder 2)
    - Commencement undated, cuid702 (Box 16C, Folder 3)
    - Convocation with Vance Packard, 1960s; cuid703 (Box 16C, Folder 4)
    - Freshmen Parents at Convocation, 1960s; cuid704 (Box 16C, Folder 5)
    - Convocation "Truth or Fiction" Lecture, 1960s; cuid705 (Box 16C, Folder 6)
    - Convocation 1960s, cuid706 (Box 16C, Folder 7)
    - Convocation 1966, 1966 December 14; cuid707 (Box 16C, Folder 8)
    - Convocation 1968-1969, cuid708 (Box 16C, Folder 9)
    - Convocation 1978, 1978 May 30; cuid709 (Box 16C, Folder 10)
    - Convocation 1979, 1979 June 6; cuid710 (Box 16C, Folder 11)
    - Convocation 2004, 2004 September 1; cuid711 (Box 16C, Folder 12)
    - Westchester Convocation, 1985; cuid712 (Box 16C, Folder 13)
    - Westchester Convocation Contact Sheets, 1986; cuid713 (Box 16C, Folder 14)
    - Honorary Degree to Carey, 1975 March 13; cuid714 (Box 16C, Folder 15)
    - Morris Chang Honorary Degree Ceremony, 1999; cuid715 (Box 16C, Folder 16)
  - Subseries C: Groundbreakings and Dedications
    - Abacus Sculpture Dedication, 1993; cuid716 (Box 17A, Folder 1)
    - Abacus, 1999 October; cuid717 (Box 17A, Folder 2)
    - Center for Finance & Technology, 1996; cuid718 (Box 17A, Folder 3)
    - Center for Fire Safety Engineering, 2002 April 9; cuid719 (Box 17A, Folder 4)
    - David Conklin Lab Dedication, 1998 May 18; cuid720 (Box 17A, Folder 5)
    - Dibner Library/CATT Building Groundbreaking, 1990; cuid721 (Box 17A, Folder 6)
    - Dibner Building Dedication, 1990; cuid722 (Box 17A, Folder 7)
    - Dibner/CATT Dedication, 1992; cuid723 (Box 17A, Folder 8)
    - Dibner/CATT Dedication- Building and MetroTech Views, 1992; cuid724 (Box 17A, Folder 9)
    - Dibner/CATT Building, 1990s; cuid725 (Box 17A, Folder 10)
    - Dibner Media Lab Dedication, 2000 April 26; cuid726 (Box 17A, Folder 11)
    - Jacobs Building and Jacobs Way Dedication, 1998 June; cuid727 (Box 17B, Folder 1)
    - Jacobs Building Groundbreaking, 2000 May 18; cuid728 (Box 17B, Folder 2)
    - Jacobs Building Groundbreaking, 2000 May 18; cuid729 (Box 17B, Folder 3)
    - Jacobs Building Groundbreaking, 2000 May 18; cuid730 (Box 17B, Folder 4)
    - Jacobs Building Groundbreaking, 2000 May 18; cuid731 (Box 17B, Folder 5)
    - Jacobs Building Groundbreaking, 2000 May 18; cuid732 (Box 17B, Folder 6)
    - Jacobs Building Construction - Soil Boring Test, 1998 November 9; cuid733 (Box 17B, Folder 7)
    - Jacobs Construction, 2001 October 5; cuid734 (Box 17B, Folder 8)
    - Jacobs Dedication Ceremony, 2002 June 13; cuid735 (Box 17C, Folder 1)
    - Jacobs Dedication Ceremony, 2002 June 13; cuid736 (Box 17C, Folder 2)
    - Jacobs Building and Othmer Residence Hall Dedication, 2002 June 13; cuid737 (Box 17C, Folder 3)
    - Jacobs Building Dedication Awards, 2002 October 23; cuid738 (Box 17C, Folder 4)
    - Topping Off Ceremony- Jacobs Building, 2001 May 18; cuid739 (Box 18A, Folder 1)
    - Topping Off Ceremony- Othmer Dorms, 2001 July 26; cuid740 (Box 18A, Folder 2)
    - Regna Lounge Dedication, 2003 October 7; cuid741 (Box 18A, Folder 3)
    - Rogers Hall Dedication, circa 1957; cuid742 (Box 18A, Folder 4)
    - Sculpture Dedication and Lynford Lecture with Robert Mundell, 2002 October 8; cuid743 (Box 18A, Folder 5)
    - Sperry Dedication, undated; cuid744 (Box 18A, Folder 6)
    - Tour of Media Lab, 1999 October 15; cuid745 (Box 18A, Folder 7)
    - Wunsch Lab Dedication, 1965 May 14; cuid746 (Box 18A, Folder 8)
  - Subseries D: Banquets and Celebrations
    - 21 Club Dinner, 1994; cuid747 (Box 18A, Folder 9)
    - Awards Ceremony, 1995; cuid748 (Box 18A, Folder 10)
    - Buecke Dinner, undated; cuid749 (Box 18A, Folder 11)
    - Corporation Dinner 1976, cuid750 (Box 18A, Folder 12)
    - Corporation Dinner 1979, cuid751 (Box 18A, Folder 13)
    - Corporation Dinner 1981, cuid752 (Box 18A, Folder 14)
    - Corporation Dinner 1982, cuid753 (Box 18A, Folder 15)
    - Corporation Dinner 1984, cuid754 (Box 18A, Folder 16)
    - Corporation Dinner 1985, cuid755 (Box 18A, Folder 17)
    - Corporation Dinner 1986, cuid756 (Box 18A, Folder 18)
    - Cuomo Dinner, undated; cuid757 (Box 18A, Folder 19)
    - Dinner with Ernst Weber, undated; cuid758 (Box 18A, Folder 20)
    - Dinners, 1967-1968, cuid759 (Box 18A, Folder 21)
    - Dinners, Undated, cuid760 (Box 18A, Folder 22)
    - Dinners and Dances, 1954-1987; cuid761 (Box 18A, Folder 23)
    - Executive Breakfast, 2000 March; cuid762 (Box 18A, Folder 24)
    - Executive Breakfast, 2003 February; cuid763 (Box 18A, Folder 25)
    - George Bugliarello Tribute, 1994; cuid764 (Box 18A, Folder 26)
    - Goldsmith's Birthday Party, 1999 October 18; cuid765 (Box 18A, Folder 27)
    - Hallingby Dinner, 1987 June; cuid766 (Box 18A, Folder 28)
    - Holiday Party 1994, 1994 December 19; cuid767 (Box 18A, Folder 29)
    - Holiday Party 1995, 1995 December; cuid768 (Box 18B, Folder 1)
    - Holiday Party 1997, 1997 December; cuid769 (Box 18B, Folder 2)
    - Holiday Party, Long Island, December 12, 1997, 1997-12-12; cuid3622 (Box 18B, Folder 3)
    - Holiday Party 1999, 1999 December; cuid770 (Box 18B, Folder 4)
    - Holiday Party 2000, 2000 December 11; cuid771 (Box 18B, Folder 5)
    - Holiday Party 2001, 2001 December 13; cuid772 (Box 18B, Folder 6)
    - Jack Kueler Dinner, 1991; cuid773 (Box 18B, Folder 7)
    - Kwanzaa Celebration, 2000 December 8; cuid774 (Box 18B, Folder 8)
    - Long Island Leadership Dinner, 1989 November 1; cuid775 (Box 18B, Folder 9)
    - Long Island Dinner 1983, cuid776 (Box 18B, Folder 10)
    - Long Island Dinner 1985, cuid777 (Box 18B, Folder 11)
    - Luncheons, 1953-1954; cuid778 (Box 18B, Folder 12)
    - PA Dinner, 1992; cuid779 (Box 18B, Folder 13)
    - Poly Ventures Dinner, 1987; cuid780 (Box 18B, Folder 14)
    - President Associate's Dinner 1987-1988, cuid781 (Box 18B, Folder 15)
    - President Associate's Dinner 1992, cuid782 (Box 18B, Folder 16)
    - President Associate's Dinner 1993, cuid783 (Box 18B, Folder 17)
    - President Associate's Dinner 1994, cuid784 (Box 18B, Folder 18)
    - President Associate's Dinner 1995, 1995 September 28; cuid785 (Box 18B, Folder 19)
    - President Associate's Dinner 1996, 1996 October 25; cuid786 (Box 18B, Folder 20)
    - President Associate's Dinner 1998, 1998 October 13; cuid787 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - President Associate's Dinner 1999, 1999 October 5; cuid788 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - President Associate's Dinner 2000, 2000 October 12; cuid789 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - President's Reception, 1983; cuid790 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Sunil's Farewell Party, undated; cuid791 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Tech Leadership Award Dinner, 1990; cuid792 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Various Dinners and Celebrations, undated; cuid793 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Westchester Dinner 1987, cuid794 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Westchester Dinner negatives 1990, cuid795 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - West Coast Tech Awards Dinner, undated; cuid796 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Subseries E: Visiting Individuals and Groups
    - Alumni Astronauts Visit, 2015; cuid797 (Box 19, Folder 10.1)
    - Betty Wu Visit, 2002 May; cuid798 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Bjarne Stroustrup Visit, 2002 April 9; cuid799 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Brooklyn Institutional Council, undated; cuid800 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Brooklyn Union Gas, 1927 October 25; cuid801 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Charles DeBenedittis Visit, 2002 October 28; cuid802 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Chinese Delegation Visit, undated; cuid803 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Con Edison Visit, 1993 May 11; cuid804 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Congelese Student Visit, 1961 November; cuid805 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - David Dibner Visit, 1998 May; cuid806 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Desiree Ruhstrat Visit, 1998 June 9; cuid807 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Eugene Kleiner Visit, 1996 September 20; cuid808 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Eugene Kleiner Visit, 1998 April 2; cuid809 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - General Council of China Visit, 1997 February 26; cuid810 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Groups- Miscellaneous, 1938-1963; cuid811 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Martin Perl Visit, 1996 May 29; cuid812 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Martin Perl Visit, 1998 May; cuid813 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Marty Markowitz Visit, 2002 February 4; cuid814 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Mayor's Cabinet Meeting, 1968; cuid815 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Michael Bloomberg Visit, 2003 August 6; cuid816 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Paul Soros Visit, 1997 April 24; cuid817 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Robert Tsao Visit, undated; cuid818 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Saul Harari Visit, 2003 November; cuid819 (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Stephen Wolfram Visit, 2003 March 5; cuid820 (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - Sumitomo Electric Inc. USA Visit, 1997 November 7; cuid821 (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Taiwan University Dignitaries Visit, 1998 August; cuid822 (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - Walter Rosenberry, 1998 September 25; cuid823 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Subseries F: Symposia and Presentations
    - ACS Symposium, 1999 April 29; cuid824 (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - Centennial Exhibit at Brooklyn Public Library, 1954; cuid825 (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - College Partnership Symposium, 1998; cuid826 (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - Conference on High Speed Aeronautics, circa 1960; cuid827 (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - Future of Telecommunications Symposium, 2005 February 11; cuid828 (Box 19, Folder 41)
    - Gene Delivery Symposium, 2000 June 19; cuid829 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Herman Mark Symposium, 1975 May 2-3; cuid830 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Herman Mark Memorial Symposium, 1992; cuid831 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Hoerscht Celanese Yearly Presentation, 1997; cuid832 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - International Conference on Business Incubation and Technology Innovation, 2000; cuid833 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Leadership Seminar 1994, cuid834 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Leadership Seminar 1995, cuid835 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Lectures/Symposia- various, 1920s - 1950s; cuid836 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Leibniz Symposium, 1960s; cuid837 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Lucent Technologies Check Presentation 1996, 1996 December 19; cuid838 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Lucent Technologies Check Presentation 1999, 1999 December; cuid839 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - ME100: 100 Years of Mechanical Engineering at Poly 1899-1999, 1999 November 4-5; cuid840 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - ME100: 100 Years of Mechanical Engineering at Poly 1899-1999, 1999 November 4-5; cuid841 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - ME100: 100 Years of Mechanical Engineering at Poly 1899-1999, 1999 November 4-5; cuid842 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - MMC-9 Conference, 2001 August 19-23; cuid843 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Othmer Symposium, 2002 October 8; cuid844 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Polymer Symposium, 1985; cuid845 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Polytechnic Centennial 1954-1955, 1954 December - 1955 July; cuid846 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Polytechnic Centennial 1954-1955, cuid847 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Polytechnic Centennial 1954-1955, cuid848 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Principal's Symposium, 1998 March-May; cuid849 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Saline Water Meeting, 1965; cuid850 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Symposium on Advances in Chelate Chemistry, 1955; cuid851 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Tic Tac Tones, 1960s; cuid852 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Urban Transportation Seminar, 1960s; cuid853 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Subseries G: Lynford Lecture Series
    - Lynford Dinner, 1997 September 24; cuid854 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Lynford Lecture Series- Ed Witten 1998, 1998 September 15; cuid855 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Lynford Lecture Series- John Craig Venter 1999, 1999 October 13; cuid856 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Lynford Lecture Series- Bill Joy 2000, 2000 October 12; cuid857 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Lynford Lecture Series- Dr. Alan Kay 2001, 2001 October 9; cuid858 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Lynford Lecture Series- Dr. Robert Mendell 2002, 2002 October 8; cuid859 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Lynford Lecture Series- Gerald M. Rubin 2003, 2003 October 20; cuid860 (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - Lynford Lecture Series- Dr. Richard L. Garwin 2004, 2004 November 4; cuid861 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Subseries H: Miscellaneous Events
    - Art Show Opening, 1998 November 19; cuid862 (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - Baby Photo Contest, 2001 January; cuid863 (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - Big Apple College Fair, 1986; cuid864 (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - Caretech, 1999 February; cuid865 (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - CATT Workshop, 1997 November 24; cuid866 (Box 20, Folder 38)
    - CATT Review Conference, 1998 October; cuid867 (Box 20, Folder 39)
    - Chinese Delegation, 1998 June; cuid868 (Box 20, Folder 40)
    - Chinese New Year's, 1995 January 31; cuid869 (Box 20, Folder 41)
    - City Hall Paint Study, undated; cuid870 (Box 20, Folder 42)
    - Co-Op Education, 1964; cuid871 (Box 20, Folder 43)
    - Colorado School Shooting Support, 1999; cuid872 (Box 20, Folder 44)
    - David Chang & Michael G. Carey, 2001 February 9; cuid873 (Box 20, Folder 45)
    - E-Commerce with Senator Schumer, 2000 August 28; cuid874 (Box 20, Folder 46)
    - Events, 1980s; cuid875 (Box 20, Folder 47)
    - Events 1992, cuid876 (Box 20, Folder 48)
    - Events 1993, cuid877 (Box 20, Folder 49)
    - Events 1994, cuid878 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Events, Miscellaneous, undated; cuid879 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Exec 21 Program, undated; cuid880 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Fall Dance, 1965-1966; cuid881 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Fire Test, 1970s; cuid882 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Foundation Grant, undated; cuid883 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Gassner Mural 2001, 2001 October 10; cuid884 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Goldsmith Opening, 1996 October 19; cuid885 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Guardian Chemical, 1960s; cuid886 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - High School Science Fair, 1997 March 26; cuid887 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Intel Science Talent Search, 1999 February; cuid888 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Israel Reunion, 1999 January 10; cuid889 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Israel Commencement, 2000; cuid890 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Israel Trip, undated; cuid891 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Jacobs Events, 1992-1994; cuid892 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Japanese TV Interview, 1992 August 11; cuid893 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Knowledge Workers Educational Alliance, 1999 October; cuid894 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Laptop Distribution, 2000 August, 30; 2000 September 13; cuid895 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Laptop Orientation, 2000 August 30; cuid896 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Logicon Technology Day, 2000, 2000 March; cuid897 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Logicon Technology Day, 2001, 2001 April 12; cuid898 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Managerial Techniques Workshop 1968, 1968 March-April; cuid899 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Mayor's Award for Excellence in Science and Technology, 2000 March 8; cuid900 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Memorial Plaque, 1973; cuid901 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Metro Cafe Awards, 2002 May 2; cuid902 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Miscellaneous Events, undated; cuid903 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Miscellaneous Events, 1936-1956; cuid904 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Miscellaneous Events, undated; cuid905 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Miscellaneous Events, undated; cuid906 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Miscellaneous Events, undated; cuid907 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Miscellaneous Events, undated; cuid908 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Multicultural Crafts Festival, 1998 December 3; cuid909 (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Natural History & Dinosaur Book Exhibit, 2000; cuid910 (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - NYC First, 2001 March 16; cuid911 (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - NYC Mathematics, Science, and Technology Fair, 1999 March 2; 2004 March 17; cuid912 (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - NYC Science & Technology Fair, 2001 May 24; cuid913 (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - NYC Science & Engineering Fair, 2002 March 13; cuid914 (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - Open House, 1997, 1997 October 26; cuid915 (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - Open House, 1998, 1998 October 25; cuid916 (Box 21, Folder 39)
    - Open House, 1999, 1999 October 24; cuid917 (Box 21, Folder 40)
    - Othmer Institute, 2001 September 4; cuid918 (Box 21, Folder 41)
    - Paint-a-thon, 1996 March 31; cuid919 (Box 21, Folder 42)
    - Poly Expo, 1992 June; cuid920 (Box 21, Folder 43)
    - Polytech Paints the Town, 1996; cuid921 (Box 21, Folder 44)
    - R & R Summer Social, 2002 June 21; cuid922 (Box 21, Folder 45)
    - Raising the Bar on Hi-Tech Incubators 2000, 2000 March 29; cuid923 (Box 21, Folder 46)
    - Science Fair, 1996, cuid924 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Science Fair, 1998, cuid925 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Science & Technology Forum, 1998, cuid926 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Science & Technology Forum, 2000, 2000 May 25; cuid927 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Sculpture Installation, 2002 October 8; cuid928 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Sculpture, 2002 October 8; cuid929 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - September 11th Poster, 2001; cuid930 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - September 11th Attack, 2001 September 14; cuid931 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Solutions at Silleck, 2001 February 28; cuid932 (Box 22, Folder 9)